Guide to the Records of Director of Academic Program Review, Barnett Hamberger 1972-2003 RG 9.7 RG 9.7
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - (Dead Coles Files) Coles Security ID, Coles Foreman Minigym Dedication, I Have A Dream, Lobby Exhibits, Sports Medicine, undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Coles Rooftop Playground, undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Coels Summer Programs, undated (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Coles Usage, 1988-1990 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Coles Usage, 1988-1990 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - UAA, 1988-1990 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - UAA, 1988-1990 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - UAA, 1988-1990 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - UAA Code of Conduct, undated (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - UAA Activities/Facilities Survey, undated (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - UAA Delegates Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225563 1
  - UAA Delegates Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - UAA Presidents Council, 1988-1990 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - UAA Presidents Council, 1988-1990 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - UAA Presidents Council, 1988-1990 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - UAA Publicity, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - UAA Schedules, 1988-1990 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - UAA Schedules, 1988-1990 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Recruitment, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Athletic Recruitment, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Recruitment, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Athletic Recruitment, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Recruitment, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Athletic Recruitment, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Athletic Recruitment, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Athletic Recruitment, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Athletic Recruitment, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Athletic Recruitment Reports, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Athletic Recruitment Reports, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Athletic Recruitment Film, undated (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Accreditation Lists, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225576 3
  - Bagpipe Band, 1988-1992 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Bagpipe Band, 1988-1992 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Bagpipe Band, 1988-1992 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Bagpipe Band, 1988-1992 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Chancellors Service Awards, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Ethnic Diversity Study Group, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Ethnic Diversity Student Subcommittee, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Ethnic Diversity Staff Subcommittee, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Ethnic Diversity Increasing the Pool, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 1991-1991 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Commission, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Commission, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Majors Registration, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Registration, 1990-1992 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Registration, 1990-1992 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Responses to SED, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Schweitzer Chair, 1989-1991 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - State Education Department, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Summer Session Liasion Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - January-December ECR's, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - January-December ECR's, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225577 1
  - Athletic Budgets, 1990-1992 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Budgets, 1990-1992 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Income Budget, 1990-1992 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Restricted Budget, 1990-1992 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Coles Budgets, 1990-1992 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Coles Budgets, 1990-1992 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Coles Plant Budgets, 1990-1992 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - FERPA Requests, 1987-1991 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - FERPA Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225575 5
  - FERPA Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - FERPA Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Athletics, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Athletics, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Academics, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Academics, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Academics, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Academics, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Athletic Academics, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Achievement Awards, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Athletic Achievement Awards, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Advisory Board, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Athletic Advisory Board, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Basketball, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Basketball, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Basketball, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Basketball, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Athletic Endowment Fund, 1988-1991 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Athletic Endowment Fund, 1988-1991 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Athletic Endowment Fund, 1988-1991 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Athletic Field Search, 1987-1992 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225562 3
  - Athletic Field Search, 1987-1992 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Field Search, 1987-1992 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Field Search, 1987-1992 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Field Search, 1987-1992 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Final Grades, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Final Grades, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Honor Roll, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Honor Roll, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Athletic News, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Athletic News, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - NCAA, 1988-1992 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - NCAA, 1988-1992 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - NCAA, 1988-1992 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - NCAA, 1988-1992 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - NCAA, 1988-1992 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Athletic Press Releases, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Athletic Rosters, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Athletic Rosters, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Coles Center, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058592 2
  - UAA Delegates Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - UAA Delegates Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - CAS, 1988-1992 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Gallatin, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Gallatin, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - GSAS, 1988-1991 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - GSAS, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - SCE, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - SCE, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - SCE, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - SCE, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - SCE, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - SEHNAP Alumni Council, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - SEHNAP Alumni Council, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - SEHNAP Alumni Council, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - SEHNAP Alumni Council, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - SEHNAP, 1990-1991 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - SEHNAP, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - SEHNAP, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Coles Registration, 1991-1992 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058576 5
  - Coles Usage, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Coles Usage, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Schedules, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Schedules, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Student Transcripts, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Student Transcripts, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Tutors, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Tutors, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Varsity Club, 1989-1991 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Varsity Club, 1989-1991 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - VBC Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - VBC Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Coles Center, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Coles Capital Reserve, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Coles Capital Reserve, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Coles Clubs, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Coles Clubs, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Coles Licensing, 1989-1991 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Coles Pro-Shop, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Coles Pro-Shop, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - UAA, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - UAA, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Coles Recreation, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Coles Recreation, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - GRE-CGS Admissions, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058574 0
  - Product List/Purchasing, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - SIS Security Committee, undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Student Athlete Study- Class of 1987-1988, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Work done Andrew, 1989-1990 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Work done Andrew, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Academic Advising Computer Project, 1988-1989 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - American Council on Education, 1987-1988 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Athletics--Summary of Recruitment Report, 1989-1990 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Athletics, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Athletics Survey Transcripts and Rosters, 1983-1985 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Coles Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Coles Usage, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Computer Proposals, undated (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Comparative Compensation, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Cornell's Top 27--Research Institutions Salary Survey, 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Cornell's Top 27--Research Institutions Salary Survey, 1986-1987 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - SEHNAP Program Terminations, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - FERPA Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - FERPA Requests, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - School of Social Work, 1988-1992 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058575 7
  - TSOA, 1988-1992 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Chronological Files, 1990-1992 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Middle States Association Off-Campus Activities Accreditation, undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225573 0
  - Affirmative Action Policy, 1991-1994 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Center for the Study in Sport, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Chancellors Service Awards, 1991-1994 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - China, 1990-1994 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Ethnic Diversity, 1990-1994 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - NYU Long-Range Plan--Report of University-Wide Planning Commission, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council, undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Facilities Classification Manual, undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Manhattanville, 1989-1994 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - MSA- LJO/Georgetown, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - MSA Revisit on the Libral Education Program, 1985-1986 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - MSA 1984 Follow Up on the Liberal Education Program (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - MSA Periodic Review Report, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - MSA Follow Up Report, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - MSA PRR Background Information, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - MSA PRR Correspondence, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - MSA Return Visit, undated (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Registration, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225570 6
  - State Master Plan Report, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Regents Statewide Master Plan, 1988-1989 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Regents Statewide Master Plan Report, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Regents Statewide Master Plan Responses, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Regents Statewide Master Plan Background Info, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Regents Statewide Master Plan Background Info, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Summer Session Liasion Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - SUNY-College of Optometry, undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Veterans Approval (SED), undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Safety Worksheets, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - APR Budget Info, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - APR Budget Info, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Coles Athletic Salary Worksheets, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Coles Athletic Salary Worksheets, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Coles Plant Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Athletics, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Athletics Academic, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Basketball Receptions, 1990-1992 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Athletics Academic Grades, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Basketball, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Basketball Attendance, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Basketball Attendance, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Basketball Away Receptions, 1990-1994 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Athletic News, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225572 2
  - Athletic News, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Parents Reception, undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Press Releases, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Press Releases, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Varsity Club, 1991-1993 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Violet Booster Club Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Fields NJ Architects, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Coles Center, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Coles Clubs, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Coles Horning, undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Coles Usage, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Coles Registration, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Coles Recreation, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - NCAA Self Study, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - UAA Special Committee: Executive Secretary Response, undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - UAA Special Committee: Executive Secretary Response, undated (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - UAA Delegate Commission, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - UAA Delegate Commission, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - UAA Delegate Commission, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - UAA Presidents Council, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - NCAA Self Study, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - NCAA Self Study, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - NCAA Self Study, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - NCAA Self Study, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - NCAA Self Study, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - NCAA Self Study, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - ACT Grad/Professional School Survey Form, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225571 4
  - ACT Institutional Data, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - American Career Expolration, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - American Council on Education- Campus Trends, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - American Universities/Colleges, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Barron's Profiles of American Colleges, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Best Colleges for African American Students, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Black Issues in Higher Education, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Cambridge Enrollment Study, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Cambridge Associates-Tuition and Board, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - CHANGE- U.S. News and Money Ranking System, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Chronicle Guidance Publication-College Charts, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Chronicle Guidance Publication-Majors, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Coles Summary, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities Campus Profile Survey, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Complete Guide to College Visits, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Municipal Bond Investors Assurance Corporation (NYU Faculty), 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Directory of Computing Facilities in Higher Education, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Dramatics-Magazine Audition Directory, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Educational Information Systems Inc.- Profiles of 4 Year Colleges and Universities, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Fiske's Guide to Colleges Questionnaire, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Government Relations re:CICU Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Guidance Information Systems- 2 year colleges, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Guidance Information Systems- 4 year colleges, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Guidance Information Systems- Grad/Prof. Survey, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Law Schools Data Survey, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Lisa Birnbach's College Book, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Mobil Travel Guide, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Money Survey- Best Buys & Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Money Guide- Best Colleges 1993, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - National Association of Colleges Stores School Year Update, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - National Beta Club College Facts Chart, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - National Research Council Survey of Ph.D. programs, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - National Survey of on-campus Housing, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Newark Star Ledger Survey, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Orchard House Inc.-College University Info. Update, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Peterson's Annual Survey of Freshman Financial Aid, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - Peterson's Annual Survey of Freshman Undergraduate Institutions, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - Peterson's Annual Survey of Graduate Institutions, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - Peterson's Guide to Graduate Studies, 1991-1993 (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - St. John's Survey re:student affairs program, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - Status of black studies, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - Survey & Publ's General, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - Peterson's Annual Survey of Higher Ed. Personnel, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - Research Libaries Annual Statistics Report, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 45)
  - USA Today College Directory Questionaiire, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 46)
  - US News & World Report- Best Buys, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 47)
  - World of Learning Guide re:Officers & Deans, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 48)
  - Yale News: Insider's Guide to Colleges, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 49)
  - Blank Forms, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence related to HEDS/HEGIS/IPEDS/NYSED forms, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 51)
  - HEDS/HEGIS Bundy Aid, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 52)
  - HEDS Fall 92 FTE Survey, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 53)
  - HEDS Graduation Rate Survey, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 54)
  - HEDS/HEGIS Due Dates, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 55)
  - IPEDS-EE Early Estimates, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 56)
  - IPEDS-EP Fall Enrollment in Occupation Specific Programs, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 57)
  - IPEDS-F1 & Suppl's 1,2- Fin'l Statistics of HE, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 58)
  - IPEDS-IC- Institutional Characteristics, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 59)
  - IPEDS-SA Salary, Tenure, & Fringe Benefits of Faculty, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 60)
  - EEO-6 HED Staff Info. From Affirmative Action Office, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 61)
  - NYSED-1-Student Admissions Info. For F/T Undergrads by Racial/Ethnic Categories, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 62)
  - NYSED-1.1 Basic Student Charges, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 63)
  - NYSED-2, 2a Earned degrees, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 64)
  - NYSED 2.1 S1 & S2- Degrees and other awards, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 65)
  - NYSED 2.3- Degree-Credit Enrollment by Subject Area for (Main, Domin. & Manhattanville), 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 66)
  - NYSED 2.4 Opening Fall Enrollment- 3 campuses, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 67)
  - NYSED 2.4A- Preliminary Degree Enrollment, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 68)
  - NYSED 2.6- HEDS Enrollment by level, age Cohort, and sex, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 69)
  - NYSED 2.7- Non credit enrollment for Main, Dominican, and Manhattanville Campuses, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 70)
  - NYSED 2.9- Graduation Rate FT UG by racial/ethnic categories, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 71)
  - NYSED 2.9A- Grad rate- postsecondary opportunities program, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 72)
  - NYSED 4.1 & copy of FISAP- Student Financial Aid Award, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 73)
  - NYSED 2X, 2X1- Work Study Estimates, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 74)
  - NYSED 5- College and Univ. Libraries, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 75)
  - NYSED 2H- Students with Disabilities, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 76)
  - NYSED- 8- Directory of Off-Campus Locations, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 77)
  - CFAE Voluntary Support Survey, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 78)
  - Requests for reports by Virginia Commonwealth Univ., 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 79)
  - HEDS/HEGIS Bundy Aid, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225574 8
  - Forms to be sent to respondents, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - HEDS/HEGIS Blank forms, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - HEDS/HEGIS Due Dates, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Reports yet to be sent, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - IPEDS-EE Early Estimates, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - IPEDS-EF1-HEDS Enrollment by Racial/Ethnic Status, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - IPEDS-F1 Fin'l Statistics of Institutions, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - IPEDS-IC- Institutional Characteristics, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - IPEDS-R1 Residence of First Time Students, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - IPEDS-SA Salary, Tenure, & Fringe Benefits of Faculty, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - NYSED 2D, 2E, 2F College of Dentistry, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - NYSED 2H- Students with Disabilities, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - NYSED 1.1- Basic Student Charges, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - NYSED 2.1 Degrees and other awards, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - NYSED 2.2.- FT UG Transfer Enrollment, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - NYSED 2, 2A Earned Degrees, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - NYSED 2.4 - Opening Fall Enrollment, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - NYSED 2.3- Degree-Credit Enrollment by Subject Area, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - NYSED 2.4A- Preliminary Degree Enrollment, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - NYSED 2.4B PT UG Degree- Credit Enrollment, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - NYSED 2.7- Non credit enrollment, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - NYSED 2.8- Residence and Migration, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - NYSED 2.9A- Grad rate- postsecondary opportunities program, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - NYSED 2.9- Graduation Rate FT UG by racial/ethnic categories, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - NYSED 2X, 2X1- Work Study Estimates, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - NYSED 4.1- Student Financial Aid, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - NYSED 5- College and Univ. Libraries, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - NYSED 7- Inventory of Physical Facilities, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - NYSED-8 Directory of Off Campus Locations, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Original Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058588 0
  - HEDS/HEGIS Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - NYSED 1.1 Basic Student Charges, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - NYSED 1 FT-U-Grad Admissions, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - NYSED 2 Cert. Of Earned Degrees, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - NYSED - 2D, 2E, 2F College of Dentistry, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - NYSED 2H- Enrollment of Disabled Students, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - NYSED 2X College Work Study Reimbursement, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - NYSED 2X.1 College W/S Actuals, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - NYSED 2.1 Degrees and other formal awards, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - NYSED 2.1 Suppl Racial/Ethnic Dist for Select., 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - NYSED 2.4 Opening Fall Enrollment, F89, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - NYSED 2.4A- Preliminary Degree-Credit Enrollment, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - NYSED 2.4B PT UG Degree- Credit Enrollment, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - NYSED 3 Emp of Inst. Of HE, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - NYSED 4.1 Student Fin Aid, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - NYSED 5- Libraries, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - NYSED 8 Dir of Off-Campus Locations, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - IPEDS--EE Early Estimates, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - IPEDS--Fiscal Indicators Report, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - IPEDS--F1 Financial Stats, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - IPEDS-IC Institutional Characteristics, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - IPEDS--SA Sal, Tenure, and Fringe FT/Fac, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - HEDS/HEGIS Due Dates, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Blank Forms, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Bundy Aid, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - HEDS/HEGIS Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - HEDS/HEGIS Due Dates, 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - NYSED--1 FT UG Adm Info by Racial/Ethnic, undated (Box 51, Folder 29)